- Oh, fuck.
Do you know where, um...
my underwear or my belt is?
Uh...
Do you speak English?
Oh!
I need it!
I-I need it.
Yo.
You here?
I'm still in Copenhagen.
Uh, is Al with you?
No. That nigga's in jail.
What? What happened?
I have no idea.
I've been roaming the streets.
High since twilight.
Darius...
This city is my Jesus.
Darius, listen,
I-I... I got a text from Van.
She's saying she's...
she's in Amsterdam.
I'm confused.
A-Are you confused?
'Cause I'm confused.
Yeah. I'll deal
with Alfred when I land.
I need you to pick up Van
- from the station, be...
Hello?
Baby mama drama.
Sorry, coming through. Sorry.
Sorry, miss.
I'm gonna let him through.
All right. Go ahead.
Yeah. Thank you.
Excuse me, sir.
I have to pat you down.
Lift up your hands, please.
I can't.
Why not?
I lost my belt.
And my underwear.
I'm sorry, sir.
I can't let you through
if you don't lift your hands.
Turn around.
Goedemorgen!
And welcome to Amsterdam!
Otherwise known
as the Venice of the North.
Hey.
- Um, Earn kind of got held up,
but, um...
Okay.
You my ride?
Yes.
Aren't you cold?
I'm fine. They lost my luggage.
Oh. Well, here,
you can wear mine.
I mean, I have been wearing it
for eight days.
- Nine days.
- No, I'm...
I'm good. You should keep it.
It looks good on you.
Thanks.
Or, um, we can go find you one.
Got the driver for the day.
You have a driver?
Yeah. Earn hooked it up.
That tour clout.
Yeah. Let's go.
So...
how's Lottie?
She's actually, mm...
she's good.
She's fine.
She's with my parents right now.
Mm.
And you and Earn?
You guys gonna...
pop out another baby?
I have a boyfriend.
Oh.
Yeah.
Why? Are you and Earn
planning on...
popping out a baby, too?
Um...
I can't procreate.
I had my balls crushed
when I was a kid in Nigeria.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Nah, it's okay.
Long time ago.
You ever seen the movie
Foodfight!?
No.
Mm. Check out the trailer.
It's...
it's intense.
Thanks.
Mm-hmm.
Dirk?
- Dirk?
Yeah.
I'm Earn.
Paper Boi's manager.
Oh, my God! Hey!
My name is Dirk.
Nice to meet you.
We are so fucking excited
for tonight.
Yeah. The show is sold out,
you know that?
- Ah.
- Sinterklaas come early
this year.
Hey, listen up. We got an idea.
We were thinking
Paper Boi can maybe wear this
to take some pictures with fans.
What do you think? Here.
With the feather.
Yeah, he's not gonna do that.
- No?
- No.
Okay.
No worries.
Who's this?
This is my taxi driver.
Cool.
He's gonna need to be paid.
It's in the rider.
It's about 40 euros,
not including tip.
Okay. I pay 40 euro.
Hey, while I got you here, um,
everything is on time
from Helsinki.
We're just missing
the music laptop.
What?
I assumed
it was with you guys, so...
No, we...
- Oh, gezondheid.
Gezondheid!
How long do we have
to get the music here?
To be safe, six hours?
Six hours. Got it.
Also, Paper Boi needs
a slight increase in his advance
before the concert tonight.
He's gonna need about 20K.
In cash.
- Uh, 20
- K when?
Right now.
- Here.
- Thank you.
20K.
Your first time in Amsterdam?
Uh, no. We actually played
a smaller venue...
last year. Yeah.
- Yeah. It's cool here, no?
- Yeah.
And the weed is
verbazingwekkend good.
And we tolerate people.
Nothing like America.
- Hey, see you tonight, guy.
- See you tonight.
I'm gonna need, uh...
some money for another cab.
This place has...
tiny steps.
Thoughts?
Mm.
Wait a minute.
Hey, come a little closer.
Yeah, you might want
to take that off.
It got gasoline on it.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, um,
I'm sorry about mentioning Earn.
I just, um... I don't do well
with small talk and...
stuff like that.
You can ask me something real.
Hmm.
Why are you here?
I was up for this job
that I wanted
and I didn't get it, so...
...thought I'd come here and...
...figure it out.
I'm gonna get this one.
Yeah, it's nice.
What's that?
Looks like an address.
Ooh.
Yeah, I know
exactly what this is.
You have to follow it.
It's destiny.
I'm down.
Say no mo'.
Man, y'all
charging me for this shit?
No cost. Whatever you like.
- For real?
- Mm-hmm.
Fuck. A'ight, cool.
A'ight, man, uh...
I'm-a get that potato mash, man.
Would you recommend
the schnitzel or the bean soup?
- The bean soup. You like it.
- The bean soup.
All right, let me get
one of the bean soups, man.
Um, look, y'all got Coke here--
Coca-Cola?
- Coca-Cola.
- Yes.
- Yes, the real one.
- All right, uh,
can I get some ice
with that, too?
- Uh, yes. Uh, cubes?
- Yeah, oh, cube, man.
Not crushed.
I don't want to chew my water.
Uh, y'all got hot sauce, right?
Yes. It's, uh, very spicy,
so maybe, uh, not too much.
Man, please, I'm from A.
Whatever you want.
- Appreciate it.
Damn, them niggas
don't let up, do they?
What they saying, man?
Uh, they say "Free Paper Boi."
"Free Paper Boi"?
- A'ight, I fuck with that.
A'ight, man. Thank you, bruh.
- Excuse me, Mr. Miles?
- Al, man.
Oh, uh, your bail has been paid,
so you're free to go.
My bail's been p...
What's your name, man?
Uh, uh, Fons.
- F-Fons?
- Yes.
Frons. Frons?
Hey, man, look,
I'm-a get my lunch first.
A'ight? And, um...
just wake me up from my nap
when it get here, a'ight?
Yes, whatever you want.
And can you turn the thermostat
down a little bit?
It's a little warm.
- Yeah.
- I appreciate that.
Should I turn off the light?
Oh, that'd be great, man. Yeah.
- Thank you. All right.
- Okay. S-See you.
Night, night.
Van? Uh, this look
like somebody else.
Yeah, let's go.
You crazy. Wait.
What are you gonna say?
I'm gonna ask
who this coat belonged to.
Hey. You're right on time.
Luke told me the van broke down.
Is he the driver?
He's the photographer.
The driver's actually...
is still in the van.
You have the address, right?
'Cause I think
we're running late.
- Oh, yes, yes.
- Yeah.
Uh, nah. I'm-I'm good, man.
Thank you.
Yeah, man,
I'm just saying, like,
whatever that fabric softener
is, bro, like...
it's fantastic.
Y-You let them know that.
That's what it...
- What up, man?
Gesundheit.
Hey, man, you got that thing
I asked you for?
Oh, y-yeah.
Um...
Bail was mad cheap,
though, so...
getting kind of nervous.
Oh, thanks, man.
I appreciate that.
- Hey!
Hey, hey. Hey!
There you go, baby.
How y'all be?
They love me here, man.
- You okay?
- No.
Fuck was up with that
midget, Don King-looking
baby back there?
Hi.
What's with all the blackface?
- Blackface?
- Oh, nigga,
stop acting like
you don't know what...
Black-- black, face, babies.
Ah.
That's, uh, Zwarte Piet.
That's, uh, for the children.
It's a long tradition passed
down for many generations, so...
Actually, he's black because
he fell down the chimney,
uh, helping, uh, Saint Nicholas.
Hmm.
- Hmm.
- Okay, well,
feels like Santa's slave,
but I respect the rebrand.
Yeah.
- He fell down the chimney,
you said?
- Yeah.
Yeah. Great guy.
Hands out candy, you know?
Who doesn't like candy?
Hi.
Thank you
Mm.
Damn.
Pretty sure that's Tupac.
- What?
- Yeah.
I felt the thug spirit
in my bones on the way up here.
I knew it.
Think about it.
There was this theory that Tupac
faked his death, right?
And then he, uh, went
to hide out in the Caribbean.
- How high are you right now?
- And there's a Dutch Caribbean.
Um...
Four? H-High four, maybe,
sliding into five.
- Sliding in...
- Pardon me.
Would you please take
a picture of us with him?
Oh, you want a pict...
All right, yeah.
Here.
Mm. Hello.
Hi.
- Oh, you probably
want landscape.
Uh...
Do you know him?
I'm his death doula.
I'm here to help my friend and
the people who love him let go.
He's dying?
Yeah, not long from now,
he will transition
out of this world
and into the next.
- Mm.
- Hmm.
May I ask what your name is?
Yeah, I'm, uh...
Vanessa.
How are you doing, Vanessa?
I'm good.
I actually flew in
from Atlanta today.
- Hmm.
- Mm-hmm.
How was your flight?
It was good. I, you know,
I... actually, I used to fly in
from Europe a lot
when I was a kid, so...
But it's just
kind of different now.
Hmm.
How so?
Uh...
I just... I'm just different.
I guess I'm-I'm just not...
I'm not a kid anymore, so...
You know.
You know, I've-I've actually,
I've been having
these panic attacks.
And I thought maybe
coming here would...
You have deviled eggs.
Oh. Yes, please, eat.
He wanted a real party.
A celebration.
Love your songs, man.
I'm glad you're with someone
who can comfort you.
Oh.
That's not my boyfriend.
- He's not my boyfriend.
- Oh.
His friend
is my daughter's father.
- Ah, I see.
- I'm actually not even here
- with my daughter's father.
- Mm.
No, I'm pretty aimless
right now.
I think you're exactly
where you're meant to be.
Hello. Please,
may I help with your...
- No, thanks.
- Nigga, if you don't get
the fuck out my face...
- You know them?
Nigga, I cannot with these
crazy hoes today.
Are they what happened
last night?
Nigga, I just said I don't want
to talk about it, all right?
What the hell happened in here?
- Oh, ooh.
- Mm.
- Oh.
Is this a nice welcome
to my country?
Oh, hell yeah. Holland slaps.
- Mm.
- Wow.
Ooh, well,
happy Sinterklaas to me.
Oh...
- What?
- De traditie is racist.
...Rihanna a "niggabitch."
- In print.
- That was een compliment.
"Yo, who's the niggabitch?"
Why'd you even repeat it?
- What, "nigga..."
Whatever, man.
Same ratchet-ass
hoes, different-ass city.
I'm just glad that girl
ain't take off with my shit.
Hey, I'm-a wash my ass.
You good?
Yeah, I'm good.
Hello?
Hi, is this
air ambulance transportation?
Sure is.
Yes, I'm in the music business.
I-I know you normally
- transfer organs,
but, uh, I'm trying
to get a laptop
that we left
at a music venue in Hels...
H-Helsinki.
Great.
It's time.
Our gorgeous friend
is ready to say goodbye.
Our duty now is to tell him
it's okay to leave us.
Does anyone want to join me?
H-He can hear you.
You can say something.
It's okay.
Oh, my God.
Thank you.
Hey, we're good to go.
We got the laptop.
Yeah, tell 'em I ain't
doing this shit, man.
What? Why?
Huh.
Hey, what's up? Y'all ready?
Yeah, um... I'll handle this.
- Okay. Mm-hmm.
- You guys go.
- Get out of here.
Try and be discreet.
Turn the clogs around, bro,
we ain't doing this shit.
Hey, homie. How are you?
I heard the laptop arrived.
Yeah.
- That's good, no?
- Yes.
Um, bad news, man. Uh,
Paper Boi's...
he's not feeling too good.
He's actually,
he's got what I got, so...
- Shit.
- Probably not gonna be able
to perform tonight.
E-Excuse me, what?
The insurance claim
should cover it.
I'll just start filling out
the paperwork
when I get to the hotel.
I'm sorry, man.
You fuck me?
Excuse me?
Do you know how many people
are waiting tonight,
and they're expecting
to see Paper Boi?
I don't know what to tell you.
Artists get sick.
Just fill out
the insurance claim.
You'll make, actually, more
money than you would've tonight.
So you do fuck me.
I don't fuck anyone.
I will destroy you.
Okay.
Hello?
What are you doing?
- Liar!
Why are you making me
do this to you, Earn?
You son of a bitch.
Why are you making me do this?
Van.
Oh, hey.
What's up?
Nothing. I got some ice.
You're getting ice
at 4:00 in the morning?
Yeah.
You good?
Night, Earn.